Michael Jackson: Searching for Neverland is a drama,
documentary film directed by Dianne Houston.
Based on the best-selling book, Remember the Time: Protecting Michael Jackson in His Final Days, and
told through the eyes of Jackson's trusted bodyguards, Bill Whitfield and Javon Beard.
The movie will reveal firsthand the devotion Michael Jackson had to his children, and
the hidden drama that took place during the last two years of his life.
Michael Jackson, played by Navi.
Bill Whitfield, played by Chad L. Coleman.
Javon Beard, played by Sam Adegoke.
Prince Jackson, played by Aidan Hanlon Smith.
Paris Jackson, played by Taegen Burns.
Blanket Jackson, played by Michael Mourra.
Michael Jackson: Searching for Neverland is a 2017 American biographical television film based on the 2014 book, Remember the Time:
Protecting Michael Jackson in His Final Days, written by Jackson's personal bodyguards Bill Whitfield and Javon Beard.
The film dramatizes Jackson in the final years of his life.
It takes place after the events of the 2004 film, Man in
the Mirror: The Michael Jackson Story.
The film explores themes of melancholy, nervous, adoring, foreboding.
The tone is emotional.